(Emily:)soldier, folder...
(Raj:)Right, yeah, right.
(Sheldon:)But...
(Raj(singing):)what do you think?
(Emily:)I think it's very cute.
(Raj:)Cute? It's not cute.
(Raj:)Cute is children dressed
as vegetables.
(Emily:)Okay, fine, it's not cute.
(Raj:)Just be honest.
You don't like it.
(Emily:)I didn't say that.
I-I just like music
you can dance to.
You can dance to this!
(Raj:)Um, uh, uh...
♪ Thor and Dr. Jones ♪
♪ One plays with lightning ♪
♪ The other plays with bones. ♪
(Raj:)I'm telling you, dude,
the song has no groove.
(Raj:)You can't dance to it.
(Howard:)Who cares?
(Howard:)I thought the whole point
of Footprints on the Moon
(Howard:)was to write songs
that make people think.
(Raj:)You can do both,
(Raj:)like Michael Jackson's
"Billie Jean."
(Raj:)While you're dancing
you're thinking, like,
"Darn it, whose baby is it?"